Alex Furlong died today. Eighteen years from now he'll be running for his life.
Freejack is a science fiction, action, crime film directed by Geoff Murphy.
Time-traveling bounty hunters find a doomed race-car driver in the past and bring him to 2009 New
York, where his mind will be replaced with that of a terminally ill billionaire.
Alex Furlong, played by Emilio Estevez.
Victor Vacendak, played by Mick Jagger.
Julie Redlund, played by Rene Russo.
Ian McCandless, played by Anthony Hopkins.
Mark Michelette, played by Jonathan Banks.
Brad Carter, played by David Johansen.
Freejack is a 1992 American science fiction film directed by Geoff Murphy and
starring Emilio Estevez, Mick Jagger, Rene Russo, and Anthony Hopkins.
The screenplay was written by Steven Pressfield, Ronald Shusett and Dan Gilroy, who
adapted it from the 1959 science fiction novel Immortality, Inc.
by Robert Sheckley.
The film was produced by Morgan Creek and released by Warner Bros.
in the United States on January 17, 1992.
It received mostly negative reviews.
The film explores themes of future, bounty hunter, based
on novel or book, chase, immortality.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.